LONDON, ENGLAND
They say if you want a
glimpse of the future...
Just look behind you.
I used to think
that was bollocks.
Now I realize...
you can't outrun the past.
When we were kids...
You'd start fights with the
toughest bastards in the yard.
But I was the one...
who were to step in and finish them.
Rest now, little brother.
While I settle your one last score.
Take care of my brother.
Anything happens to him...
I'll come back looking for you.
Here.
Hold this.
FAST & FURIOUS 7
Come on, Dom, so where
are you taking me?
They say an open road helps you think...
about where you've been...
where you're going.
So you don't remember any of this yet?
It's not fair.
You know I don't.
So what is it exactly that
you're trying to show me?
That.
Race Wars.
We used to come here?
"Come here"?
We invented it.
RACE WARS
Keep it under 9000 rpms.
Kid's gonna fire his
pistons after the first 200.
You know that's not my style,
I got to ride or die, right?
How about you just ride on this one.
Are you ready?
I know you're ready!
Go!
(crowd cheering)
Nice job!
Hey!
That's the girl I heard so much about.
Where you been at, ghost girl?
That's the girl...
Ghost girl...
Letty, what the hell?
Damn, Dom! Your girl's
still got that swing, homie.
You never could take a punch.
Right, right.
Hey, man, I'm glad you're back,
man. It's good to see you.
Good to see you, Héctor.
Alright. We made it, Jack.
- Yeah, we made it!
- Yeah, we made it.
I just gotta, find
that door button.
Buddy where's the door
button at? Do you know?
- Hey.
Yeah, of course.
I'm new to this.
Yeah, you don't seem
like the minivan type.
No, not exactly.
Hey buddy you didn't give me
a high-five? Wait, wait, wait.
High-five! All right! Yeah, buddy.
Appreciate it, thank you.
Don't worry, you'll get used
to this in no time.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
First time I saw this...
I thought it was kind of funny.
I guess now, the joke's on me.
What are you doing?
What I should've
done a long time ago.
Stop!
Look at it.
It's the truth.
-------
That's the date that I lost my memory.
That's the date that Letty died.
And I was born.
No.
You never died.
Do you know how hard it is
for me when you look at me?
And you see me through
15 years of memories?
Every beautiful moment we've ever had.
I see it in your eyes.
I can't give that to you.
I got nothing.
You got me.
And you've got only a piece of me.
I have to find myself.
For me.
Goodbye, Dom.
DIPLOMATIC SECURITY SERVICE
LOS ANGELES DIVISION
--------
You're disappointed, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
The last arrest.
It was too easy.
Target didn't even run.
Ah, it's okay.
Gives me a chance to hit the iron.
Also, lets me work on
my stamping skills.
You're a terrible liar.
See you tomorrow, boss.
- I'll see you then.
- Don't stay too late.
I'll stay as long as I want, woman.
I knew you'd say that.
Elena?
What's this?
It's the letter of
recommendation you asked for.
Just know I meant
every word in there.
Thanks, Hobbs.
Thanks for everything.
Come on, way too sentimental right now.
Get home.
Good night.
Okay. Bye.
Just one sec.
You sure as hell ain't the IT guy
so you better start talking...
before I break that
finger six different ways...
and stick it straight right
where the sun doesn't shine.
Agent Hobbs, right?
That's right.
I'm also the last man on Earth whose
computer you wanna be hacking into.
You just earned yourself a
dance with the devil, boy.
You're under arrest.
Like I said, I'm here for the
team that crippled my brother.
There ain't no goddamn team.
It was just one man, and he's
standing right in front of you.
The lady was right.
You are a terrible liar.
Goddamn IT guys.
Hobbs!
On me!
Elena!
Hobbs?
Hobbs!
-----------
Alright buddy, we gotta
go or we'll be late.
Come on.
Okay, uhh.
What do you think?
Parking brake slide
right up to the school?
Where's mommy?
I don't know.
She's up there. She's coming.
Oh.
Watch your head.
Dom, you have a package out here.
From Tokyo.
Tokyo?
What's Han trying, to convert
me over to a turbo charger?
You ready?
There we go.
Hey buddy, cars don't fly.
Hey, cars don't fly.
This one did, huh?
Brian in a minivan.
Things have changed.
He's struggling, Dom.
He doesn't want me to see it...
but the white picket fence is
like an anchor for him. I can tell.
I tried to talk to him the other
night. Do you know what he said?
He doesn't miss the girls.
He doesn't miss the cars.
He misses the bullets.
Let him settle in.
Give him time.
How does nine months sound?
I'm having another baby.
And you didn't tell him, did you?
You gotta tell him.
I don't want him to be
disappointed with this life.
With me.
He will never be disappointed with you.
You're the best thing
that's ever happened to him.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Dominic Toretto.
You don't know me.
You're about to.
Private number
Tokyo, Japan
Get down!
Jack!
Shattered his collarbone,
fractured his leg in two places.
He only regained
consciousness this morning.
First thing he said was,
"Get me Dom".
He's in there.
You okay?
I'm fine.
He's waiting. Let's go.
Got something for you.
Your files.
Thank you.
You risk life and limb
to save the free world...
and what do they give you?
Jell-O and a bad 70's TV show.
Y'know, it's got its perks.
Sponge baths ain't that bad.
Dad!
I'm sorry, baby.
"Dad"?
Honey, I want to
introduce you to somebody.
He's a, uhh...
He's an old friend.
Go on and say hello.
Dominic Toretto, right?
My dad said, he kicked your ass once.
Who did this?
You remember Owen Shaw?
The one we tore half of
London down trying to get.
Well...
This is his big, bad brother.
Take a look at this.
-----------
"Deckard Shaw"
British Special Forces assassin.
The kind of unique asset...
that no government would
ever admit to employing.
Black Ops boys.
Worse. They created a monster.
They felt Shaw was a necessary
evil until eventually...
they decided he was unnecessary.
The powers that be, felt that he
knew just a little bit too much.
The asset became a liability.
So they sent in 20 elite
operatives to retire him.
And they missed.
That was 6 years ago and Shaw's
been a ghost ever since.
Until now.
How do I find him?
The official answer is: you don't.
He killed Han.
Almost killed my family.
He also tried to put
me in a body bag, too.
Which is why when I get out, I'm
gonna put a hurt on him so bad...
he's gonna wish his mother
had kept her legs closed.
But until then, my official answer to you...
is stand down.
Now you know I can't do that.
I do know you, Dom.
Which is why now I give you
a brother to brother answer.
You do whatever it is you gotta do.
When you find that sumbitch...
Just do me one favor.
What's that?
Don't miss.
MONTECRISTO,
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
Thank you so much for
letting us stay, Mando.
I hope it's not a problem.
Listen, Dom needed a safe
delivered to Rio in two days.
That was a problem.
Hosting his family in
the Dominican Republic,
that is vacation.
Anyone messes with you here...
they're messing with
the entire country.
You'll be safe.
Yeah, they're here. I picked
them up myself at the airport.
Hold on. Your brother.
Dom.
Yeah, Mia, it's me.
How's it going there?
We're at Mando's. This
place is like a fortress.
You should see Brian.
He's in full FBI mode.
He built a surveillance hub in
Mando's garage and everything.
What about you? Did you find
out who's after us?
Looks like the sins of
London have followed us home.
How did Buster take the news?
I can't tell him.
If he knew about the baby,
he'd stay here with us.
And with all that's going on, you're
gonna need him by your side.
Just watch out for
him. Keep him safe.
And come home together.
Tell Brian I'll see
him in LA in two days.
Where are you going?
Tokyo.
I'm bringing Han home.
Authorities are still
trying to determine...
the motive behind this daring
attack here at the office...
of the US Diplomatic Security Service
in downtown Los Ángeles...
less than 36 hours ago.
Facts are still coming in...
but what is known is the suspect
entered the building's 4th floor...
Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
This guy's just, relentless.
That's why Dom needs you.
You two need to find this
guy and you need to stop him...
before he does any more
damage to our family.
I just...
I've screwed up so many things.
I couldn't live with myself
if I screwed this up, too.
You won't.
I believe in you.
I believe in us.
That's all that matters.
I love you, Brian.
Love you, baby.
Just promise me.
After this, we're done.
No more jobs, no more enemies.
Come back to us.
I won't let you down, Mia.
I know.
TOKYO, JAPAN
Hey yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here
wanna race the new DK.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
He said he knew Han.
Han said you was fast,
but not that damn fast.
Who said American muscle can't drift?
Han mentioned he left his
enemies in his rear view.
He never talked about it much.
Always playing it
close to the vest.
We found a couple of
things by the crash.
Wasn't much left.
Gisele.
Yeah.
There's one more thing.
I found this.
Must've meant something to him.
When you find the
guy that killed Han...
What are you going to do?
Words ain't even been invented yet.
They say to live in the hearts
of those we leave behind...
is not to die.
But he put you in his grave.
So now I'll do the same to him.
I can't do no more funerals.
First, Han...
Now Hobbs is laid
out, of all people.
We're being hunted.
You know he's out there
somewhere watching, right?
I hope so.
That means he's close.
Just promise me, Brian.
No more funerals.
Just one more.
His.
------
You never should've
messed with a man's family.
I told your brother the same thing.
Reinforced your chassis.
Just like going into the
ring with weighted gloves.
Your mistake. I'm not
here to play games.
See, you and me...
We're from different worlds.
Trust me, I've seen a lot meaner
streets than the ones you're used to.
Stick around.
It's gonna get a lot meaner.
You think this was
gonna be a street fight?
On the ground!
Now!
Drop him or I will drop you!
Woah, woah!
Easy, guys. We're on
the same team here.
Mr. Toretto...
I'm here on the recommendation...
of a, mutual friend of ours.
- Mr. Hobbs?
- Who the hell are you?
Me? I'm just a guy.
I'm, Mr. Nobody.
That's a big entrance for a nobody.
And the guy who put our
mutual friend in the hospital...
you just let him get away.
I think I might've just
saved your ass there, Dom.
Listen, you think you can
let go of my guy there?
He's beginning to turn a little blue.
I appreciate that.
Here they come.
Listen, Dom.
There's a war going on between
shadows and ghosts like me.
You and your team unwittingly walked
into the middle of it in London...
and it appears it's
now followed you home.
It's up to you.
I'm gonna have a beer.
You're welcome to join me.
By the way, I can get you Deckard Shaw.
BASE OF OPERATIONS
EL SEGUNDO, CALIFORNIA
Belgian ale.
Man, those monks got it right.
I don't know about the whole celibacy
thing, but when it comes to beer...
Would you like one?
I'm more of a Corona man myself.
Your files, not only detailed...
It's, extremely entertaining.
Look, Shaw's power is
that he's a shadow.
He's really good at getting
in and out of places...
without being seen and leaving
nothing but a body count in his wake.
He's a legitimate English badass.
But to be honest with you Dom, I don't
give two shits about Deckard Shaw.
It's you I want.
Because you and I can help
each other get what we both need.
I'm listening.
Just recently, a
private military company...
led by a wanted terrorist
named Mose Jakande...
kidnapped a hacker known
only by the name "Ramsey".
Lady Liberty's got her panties in
a bunch over this but rightfully so...
because this Ramsey has
created something interesting.
- Bring it up.
- Yes, sir.
Say hello...
To God's Eye.
Now this little bastard hacks into
anything that's on a digital network.
That means every cellphone,
satellite, ATM machine, and computer,
simultaneously.
If it's got a microphone or a lens,
God's Eye can use it to find you.
So you invited me here to
show me a tracking device.
On steroids. Lots of them.
Let me put it
to you this way.
It took us nearly a decade
to find Osama bin Laden.
With this, we could locate
him anywhere on the planet
in a couple of hours.
Now that's a serious
piece of machinery...
that could be catastrophic
in the wrong hands.
But for some very
nauseating, political reasons...
any rescue plans involving any
US government forces or entity...
has been strictly ruled out.
And that's why I need you.
But why do I need you?
I mean I could go back outside,
enjoy the rest of the Coronas...
let Shaw come to me.
You could do that. How's that
working out for you so far?
You got one friend in the ground,
another one in the hospital...
and then of course there's that
little issue of the bomb...
that destroyed your home.
Shaw lives in a world that
doesn't play by your rules.
Like it or not...
you live in that world now, too.
You wanna know how to kill a shadow?
You just shine a little light on it.
If you get the God's Eye for me...
I've already got authorization for
you to use it until you get Shaw.
You go from the hunted, to the hunter.
And there's no place on
Earth Shaw can hide from you.
More importantly,
you and your family...
don't go to any more funerals.
You get Ramsey, you get the God's Eye...
You get Shaw.
Well that's the windup and the pitch.
Now that I've given you this incredibly
sensitive and highly classified information...
What do you think, Toretto?
I think you already
know what I'm gonna do.
Good.
But, it'll be my way.
And my crew.
I assumed you might say that.
Which is why I've taken the
liberty of gathering your team.
This is crazy.
What the hell is going on in here?
Our intelligence suggests that
Ramsey will be transported...
by an armed motorcade through
the Caucasus mountain range.
If they clear this range
and reach their destination...
Ramsey's as good as gone.
So let me get this straight.
There's only one road
that leads in or out...?
Sheer drops on every side...
A motorcade from hell
protected by a small army...
from one mile on either direction?
Yeah, that's about it.
- You done?
- No, I'm not done.
So you all wanted me to break
into a police station, fine.
Then you asked me to stop a tank.
I wasn't happy about it, but I did it.
Then you came up with
this brillant idea...
to shoot down one of the
largest airplanes, ever.
I shot that shit outta the sky...
It's nothing.
But this right here, my friend...
happens to be the stupidest idea
I've ever heard of in my life.
I forgot that, you were the only
one to bring that plane down.
No, only thing I've ever seen
him take down was "No knees" Denise.
Remember? At prom?
Really, Brian? You're gonna
do that right here?
See, y'all try'na
get me off my point.
All I'm saying is, I'm
tired of everybody around me...
making all the decisions.
This time, I lead.
Seriously. If I don't
start making decisions, I'm out.
All right, Roman.
What do you got?
I mean, I wouldn't try to get into
the whole leadership thing, like, now.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm just kind of...
Talking about like, at some point.
Like, you know, when we...
Whatever. I mean, I think...
Let's hit it from here.
- I don't think that that's...
- No, don't think.
That's my job.
Okay.
It is impossible to hit it there.
That is literally the most
secure spot on the mountain.
Why? Because you cannot
physically access it.
Now see, that's what makes it so sweet.
Because it's the place that they
least expect us to hit them from.
As much as I hate to admit it,
he's on to something there.
What do you think, Dom?
Here?
Yeah.
I think we got a plan.
Completely wrong thinking.
And I like it.
- You see?
- I'm good at this.
Good?
Okay.
How are you planning on
getting on that road?
Well, Tej?
I think I may actually
have a plan for that.
What? I delegated.
That's what good leaders do.
Leader!
You know, when I was
reading your files...
I was impressed with what you've
accomplished with your team.
But, meeting them
now I gotta say, Dom...
you truly have a gift.
Consider my workshop
your new playhouse.
I think you'll find our cars...
extremely appealing.
And your team...
is now complete.
I went to the house.
I was looking for you everywhere.
You scared the shit outta me.
You will never be alone...
(inaudible voices)
Where did you find that?
Found it in Han's car.
It was left as a message.
A message I plan on returning.
Can you ride?
Yeah, of course I can.
Han was my family, too.
Brian!
We're gonna need long
travel suspension...
limited slip differentials
in all of them.
How you doing.
Tej!
I want the demon
lovechild between that...
and that.
That's a lot of armor.
Just gonna add more
weight, slow you down.
This time it ain't
just about being fast.
Yeah, I'm good.
From the streets, you
know what I'm sayin'?
It's nothing.
Hey, Roman, you're
freaking out, ain't you?
- No.
- Yeah, you are.
I said, no.
Listen man, it takes a grown man
to embrace his feelings.
If you need to cry,
just go ahead and cry.
As your friend, you know I'm
concerned about your well-being.
Which is why I took the precaution...
of putting some adult diapers
in your glove compartment.
Can you just chill out, man?
I have seen some crazy shit, Dom,
but this really could make some waves.
So let's just try to keep it
as low key as possible, huh?
Don't I always?
I tell you what: you knock it down
a couple of notches this time...
and I'll swap out my
Belgian for a keg of Corona.
You'd be doing yourself a favor there.
Can somebody just walk me through
what we're supposed to be doing here?
Come on, Rom. This was
your plan, you gotta embrace it.
No, this was not my plan.
Yeah, here we go. Gametime.
Roman, you need some fresh air?
'Cause you about to
get a whole lot of it.
Okay, here we go!
Just when you didn't think it
can get any better, huh?
Oh, shit!
Now we're moving.
Everybody good?
Everybody make it out?
You should tell 'em,
that this is not for you!
This is not your mission!
Rom, what's up man!
Talk to me, come on!
- I can't do it.
- The hell, you can't!
Come on man! You throw that thing in
reverse and get your ass out here now!
Look I can't do it, okay?
Listen to what I'm saying.
Now isn't the time!
I'mma stay up here with the pilot.
We're gonna circle around and make sure
we're holding them down from up here!
We're running out of time!
The chute is guided by GPS!
You don't have to do anything!
- Tej!
- I'm already on it.
Listen, man. Listen
I'm sorry to let y'all down, okay?
I'mma go ahead and stay up here.
No, brother.
- I'm sorry to let you down.
- What?
Is that...?
Tej! What are you doing?
No!
Tej!
I hate you, Tej!
Get ready!
Ground's coming fast!
C'mon, baby.
Come on.
Touchdown, baby!
Car check. Call it in.
- Check.
I'm good, let's do this.
Hello? Please man!
Get me outta here, somebody!
No! The trees!
Shit.
Sit tight, Roman.
We'll come back for you.
This is not the plan!
CAUCASUS MOUNTAINS,
AZERBAIJAN
All right.
You got one chance to
hit them here, Dom.
You miss, they'll make it
to their black site...
they'll squeeze whatever
information they need out of Ramsey.
The device and your chance of ever
getting Shaw will be gone for good.
That ain't gonna happen.
I'll see you at the pickup.
Ramsey, will be in the bus.
Then let's do this.
Captain we have company.
Four cars inbound.
What, no!
- Tej, shoot it!
- I'm on the way!
All right, formation!
Bulletproof, baby.
Punch it!
Strike!
Guns, free.
Yes, sir.
No!
Shit!
Get out of the way!
Those aren't guns,
those are goddamn cannons!
Armor piercing rounds!
Hook 'em up.
Brian, Tej, blow it!
Lock it up.
Brian, you're up!
Little closer, Tej!
Ramsey?
Stay away from me!
Stay back!
Don't you touch me!
My name's Brian, and I'm
gonna get you out of here...
but I'm gonna need you
to settle down, all right?
I'm gonna cut those
things off of you.
Sir?
Sir, we have an
unidentified vehicle approaching.
Come on! Closer!
You have to jump!
We're out of time. Come on.
We gotta get out of here!
Come on!
Look at me!
If you don't jump,
we're gonna die! Okay?
You're jumping. Come on!
One.
Two!
Well, well, well.
Take my hand!
Welcome to the party, Mr. Shaw.
Letty, stay with Brian.
Oh shit!
What are you doing?
This is crazy!
Keeping you alive!
There's a cliff.
Cliff! cliff!
No!
Too slow!
Yeah!
I'm back, bitches!
You good?
Thank you.
Roman! Get back to the others.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
I have to say, I am impressed.
I would very much
like to know the name...
of the man who is
causing me so much trouble.
There is no way out of there.
What is he doing?
He's frozen like a
damn deer on headlights.
Toretto ain't no deer.
Come on, Dominic.
Give us the girl,
and I'll let you live.
What are you going to do?
You might wanna put on
your helmet for this one.
Target the driver!
Dammit! What is he thinking?
You're insane!
You're pointing the wrong way!
Am I now?
Fire on my mark.
Interesting.
Three!
Two!
Hold on.
One!
Fire!
Looks like our demon lovechild worked.
That's one way down a mountain.
Where's Ramsey?
Hello Kitty's awake.
She don't look
like a hacker to me.
Oh yeah? And what
do hackers look like?
They don't suppose to look...
like that.
I'm just saying, like, how they
normally wear them li'l weird glasses...
that's all crooked, with pimples all
over they face from drinking soda.
I mean trust me,
with a body like that...
I ain't gonna park
it behind a computer.
How you feeling?
Did you hit your head?
Feeling nauseous?
Ears ringing?
No?
Where's my shoe?
It flew off when you crashed.
When you start experiencing any
of those things, let me know. Okay?
I don't know whether to
thank you for rescuing me...
or to kick your ass for
throwing me off a cliff.
Thank us or kick our ass, huh?
How about you tell us
where that device is?
I mailed it to a friend.
In Abu Dhabi.
That was pretty easy.
That other team would've
tortured you for that information.
I didn't trust them.
I trust you.
Now why would you trust
us? You barely know us.
I know enough.
Ex-cop. Military,
something like that.
The way you took out
those guys, serious training.
Tech guy. Offended by the
hacker remark, naturally.
Alpha.
Mrs. Alpha.
Joker.
Wrong.
Double Alpha.
Man-candy. Y'know
what I'm saying?
Man, sit your candy-ass down.
The disrespect is real around here.
Life is binary. Zeroes and ones.
Only two things keep a
group like this together.
Fear or loyalty.
And I don't see a drop
of fear among you guys.
Very impressive.
Just one thing.
They're not married.
She's so off as crack,
you're just gonna roll with it?
You're telling me there can't
be a double alpha in one group?
You work for the US government?
We got similar interests.
Tej, call it in.
We're going to the Middle East!
Hey, Dom, it was pretty
wild in that mountain, huh?
That was too close.
But we got the job done.
Know what the crazy thing is? It's...
You missed the bullets.
That's messed up, huh?
Brian, I've seen you jump
from trains, dive from planes.
Hell, I saw your courage
the day I met you.
Right.
You wanna know the bravest
thing I've ever saw you do?
Be a good man to Mía.
Being a great father
to my nephew, Jack.
Everyone's looking
for their thrill...
but what's real,
is family.
Your family.
Hold on to that, Brian.
UNITED ARAB EMIRATES
This was hotter than
I thought it would be.
Yeah, well, we are in the
desert so, it would be hot.
No, I ain't talking
about the weather.
My, my, my.
Now that, is a woman that's worth
falling out a plane for.
Get outta there, man. I got dibs on
that. You see me looking at that.
Did you just say "dibs"?
What are you, in the fourth grade?
Man, can you just get outta there?
It's a free market.
What are you talking about?
- Get outta that.
- Free.
Rock, paper, scissors for it.
Are you guys for real right now?
Look at you.
You both look whooped
already. You got stalker eyes.
I tried to call dibs
on Ramsey. Two years ago.
Her knee, my balls.
Trust me, you don't wanna do that.
Hey! Ramsey!
Hello, Zafar.
So you made some new friends.
Yeah, some short-
tempered new friends.
I need the speed drive
I sent you. Where is it?
Oh good, you will be
pleased to know. I sold it.
You sold it?
You hear that?
I asked you to take care of it.
Why on Earth would you sell it?
We're gonna need it back.
Impossible.
Zafar, I stashed something
inside it. It's important.
Okay.
Good news: It is safe.
And the bad news?
It is very safe.
Sold it to a Jordanian
prince living up there.
Trust fund billionaire.
Said he wanted it
in his supercar.
Now see, this...
This I like.
Billionaire, supercar.
What makes it so, "súper"?
242 mile per hour, top speed.
And, it's bulletproof.
Am I the only one around right now?
It's like, y'know what I'm sayin?
.....
Whatever.
Where does he keep it?
In his penthouse.
Tower number one.
Now why in the hell would he
keep his car in his penthouse?
He's a billionaire, my friend.
He can do whatever he wants.
Now, tomorrow happens to be
the longest day of the year.
Prince wants to celebrate it,
host a party, tomorrow afternoon.
So you can get us up there, right?
Sure.
But not dressed like that.
What?
Something wrong?
There's a billion things wrong.
But not in this moment.
You look handsome.
I feel awkward.
You and me both.
Seeing you dressed like this...
Just reminds me of something.
Of what?
Old times.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine .
Showtime.
No, listen, man.
They're telling me they
party like this everyday,
on this level, they party everyday.
This is crazy. I might
have to move out here.
I think I'mma start a new
culture. It's called "Blarab".
You know, like Black Arab?
How are we looking, Tej?
We're almost in position.
Okay, so this is how we work this.
We gotta move in sync if we're
gonna pull this off so let's...
go over it to make sure everyone
clearly understands their role.
Roman, that means you.
You know what? You're being real
unprofessional right now, Tej.
The God's Eye chip is hidden in a speed
drive installed in the prince's car...
which he keeps in a safe room vault.
Now I make 8 to 10
playing closed security.
Not to mention the prince...
and his personal bodyguards.
Security cameras are
clustered by the north wall
that's where the vault is.
Now to get in that vault, we gotta
tap into the security system...
which can be accessed in
the prince's bedroom.
Alright, guys.
I'm going in.
Excuse me.
I was just looking for...
- The party is that way.
- What?
This room is off...
Now once we're tapped in
Ramsey and I can hack into
the network and pop the door
so you can get in
and get that chip.
Wait, wait. You missed a step.
What about my steps?
What am I supposed to be doing?
No, we didn't miss anything.
You're special team,
so when we need you...
do what you do best.
And that is?
Shine brightly, like
only Roman Pearce can do.
Now we're talking.
Alright, Tej. I'm in.
Find a phone jack. The
tap always runs behind that.
It's gonna be a 350
mega Hertz CAT5 D cable.
They probably got a
couple dozen back there.
But this'll be the bonded
pair with a plenum coat.
English, Tej.
It'll be the orange wire.
Alright, ladies and gentlemen,
we are in the pilot's seat.
Alright, Roman.
Do whatever it is you do.
It's your birthday, right?
Are you Jasmine?
God, no. Not the birthday routine.
Happy birthday to you. This way.
Excuse me, so sorry. I'm
coming through, sorry.
Right this way.
Listen, excuse me one second.
Man, you ain't...
Sir, thank you so much.
Listen, people. Please
everybody, gather around.
Understand something right now.
Listen to what I'm telling y'all.
We are here to celebrate
Jasmine's 18th birthday.
Happy birthday, my dear.
Happy birthday to you.
To you.
I wish I didn't see that.
Ramsey, open it up for us.
Copy that.
You're in.
You realize what this is?
Lykan HyperSport.
$3.4 million. 0 to 60
in less than 30 seconds.
There's 7 of these things in the world
and this guy keeps it locked up in a vault.
Nothing's sadder than
locking a beast in a cage.
Right now I really wanna
punch him in the face.
Okay.
Let's get to work.
You got this, right?
Go.
All right.
Would you believe I knocked
him out with my charm?
You ain't that charming, bitch.
Intruders.
Lock it down.
No!
Tej, our magic trick is
failing. We're losing systems.
I know.
I see it.
Tej, talk to me.
I'm trying but their security
system is locking us out.
Listen, ladies and gentlemen...
Oh, there he is.
These your dancers?
This is a party, baby!
Some of ya'll probably
went to the bathroom
and noticed that all the
hairspray was missing.
Yep. She did it.
Thank you.
And we're so happy
for you to be here.
You look like you got some
missiles underneath that dress.
He did not just...
Did you just say that?
Shit! Not the gate!
Brian, faster!
We're playing all the
defense we can up here.
But we're gonna lose, you gotta hurry up.
Thank god, you showed up.
These parties bore me to death.
Guys get out of there right now.
You've got an army headed your way.
Brian, get up! Forget it!
Tej, we're taking the car.
This is what I do.
Y'know what I'm sayin'?
Letty, Letty, talk to me.
Are you okay?
Guys I can't hold it.
I'm losing the final gate.
You gotta get out of there.
Tear off the dash!
Go through it.
Wait, just hold on man.
Time to unleash the beast.
Go!
Stay with me, I got you.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Dom. Cars don't fly!
Cars don't fly!
Shit!
No brakes!
What?
- No brakes!
- Shit!
No!
- Got it!
- Get out!
TORRES ETHIHAD Abu Dhabi
Still miss the bullets, Brian?
There they are, disaster.
I'm sorry.
I get you an invite to the most
exclusive party in Abu Dhabi.
Zafar.
No, no, you steal the host's car.
And you jump it between two buildings.
Actually, it was three buildings.
Oh! Two, insult.
Three, honor. My bad
Wow, wow, wow.
I have to say...
You've got an interesting interpretation
there of low key, Mr. Toretto.
I thought we had an understanding.
Sometimes you have to
play the hand you're dealt.
That's why I prefer
to be the dealer.
Good night.
Kicked out of my own garage.
This is great.
May I?
Brian.
Give it to him.
All that trouble for
this little.... thing.
With all due respect, Dom...
You really did great work
back there. All of you.
All of my men are now standing by...
and are fully at your disposal.
Your call.
Ramsey.
Fire it up, and find me Shaw.
Damn, this is crazy.
Thank you.
Give me a second.
What is it doing now?
It's hunting.
Hacking into the security
cameras at Ethihad Towers.
That's the last place we saw
Shaw so that's where we start.
That's him, right there.
Wait. What are these
numbers out here for?
It's biomapping Shaw's face.
It will run that against every camera...
Every audio device in this hemisphere.
Bingo. Looks like he's holed up here.
That's perfect.
Automated factory, no
people. Lots of places to hide.
You just changed the
face of manhunts forever.
Congratulations.
Can I check my e-mail real quick?
Dawn's up in two hours.
We're gonna go take down Shaw then.
Go get changed.
We should go now.
Just you, your team and me.
I thought you said at dawn?
My guys are racers.
Best drivers in the world.
But they ain't killers.
Told you he'd say that.
I know you too well, Dom,
and I'm going with you.
Looks like we got a
nice little hunting party.
Let's go bag a shadow.
Ten clicks out, boys. Get
ready to rock and roll.
Here we go. Weapons hot.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
I hope you're enjoying your last meal.
This is it?
This is all you want?
A dozen men?
I think you'll find
it's more than enough.
I'm ready to meet my maker.
Are you?
What were you expecting,
Toretto? Catch me off guard?
Me standing here,
waving a white flag?
Have you ever heard the saying:
"The enemy of my enemy...
is my friend"?
I don't have friends.
I got family.
Well, I got a lot of friends.
Keep your formation!
Sheppard, clear one!
Brian, leave it!
Get down!
I got you.
The God's Eye.
You didn't really think I was
gonna walk in there naked, did you?
You got hit bad.
Look. Toretto.
I know you won't listen to me.
You're not gonna wanna
hear what I have to say.
But the truth is...
you really ought to...
try that Belgian ale, man.
It's something special.
Belgian ale, huh?
We gotta get you to a hospital.
No, you're not.
I carry my own health insurance.
SOCOM Medics on standby.
They're already inbound.
Pull over, kid.
Dom, you got to protect Ramsey.
As long as she's alive,
she can lock them out of
God's Eye and they know that.
That means, they're not gonna stop
coming until they've got her.
And this time when they come...
They're gonna come with
everything they've got.
I'm not leaving you.
You're not.
I'm leaving you.
Go now, Dom.
A war is coming to us
whether we like it or not.
But if a war's coming...
We're gonna face them on
the streets we know best.
I'm all for winging it,
but this is crazy, man.
We got mercenaries with
some real heat on us.
I mean I ain't scared
of nothing but...
..I don't even have a gun.
Gun?
We got a whole city.
And we may have more than that.
If they use God's Eye...
it will tap the cameras
around to find our location.
Which means we could plant a virus.
And then break in when they access it.
So you're talking about
hacking my hacking device.
That's brilliant.
Yeah, but there's one problem.
The signal strength.
We can't start a hack on them until
they're within a two mile range.
- That's really close.
- Close?
These guys are military.
If they're within two miles
of us, we already dead.
I don't know about y'all, but
I didn't really plan on dying today.
Only one way to stay alive.
We play keepaway with Ramsey.
What?
They can't hit us
if we keep moving.
And I'll take Shaw.
So basically we're just gearing up
for a big game of hot potato, huh?
Why does it feel like
I'm not gonna see you again?
I'll come back for that.
Promise?
Promise.
Brian, are you okay?
Mía, listen to me.
Something's about to go down.
If you don't hear
from me in 24 hours...
I need you to take Jack and move on.
You understand?
You understand what I'm saying?
No I can't do that, Brian.
No, I can't.
We're gonna have another baby.
It's a little girl.
And she's going to need her father.
So you have to finish
what you're doing...
and you have to come home to her.
You have to come home to us.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you before.
I was scared you'd be
disappointed with domestic life.
You know the best decision I ever
made was stepping into that store...
buying that first sandwich.
It was such a bad sándwich.
I know.
But I ate a lot of 'em.
I love you, Mía.
Don't do that.
What?
The way you said it.
It's like goodbye.
Say something else.
Okay. Kiss Jack for me.
I will.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, Mía.
One last ride.
Boot up God's Eye, and find them.
-------
I'm getting something.
I got a positive ID. It's Toretto.
God's Eye is placing
him at Hill and Seventh.
Should we follow him?
No. Let Shaw take care of him.
Find Ramsey.
Yes, sir.
I don't know why we gotta
keep driving around like this.
Why can't we just
pull over somewhere...
park, gather our thoughts in
like a bunker somewhere?
Because it does not work like that.
We gotta stick close
enough to the bad guys...
in order to get in
range for Ramsey to hack 'em...
but we gotta be mobile enough not
to get shot like fish in a barrel.
So do me a favor, focus on the
mission, keep us from getting killed.
Got them. Target acquired.
She's riding shotgun in a blue GT-R.
Guys, they're here.
How many cars?
None.
And that's kind of the problem.
Let's give them a tour.
Break on my mark.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Splitting up won't work.
You can't hide from God's Eye.
In range.
Ramsey, start the hack.
Initiating.
Now.
-------
Sir, I think someone's
trying to hack the system.
It's Ramsey.
Send in the predator!
Take her out!
Releasing predator.
I think we lost the chopper.
I think we got bigger
problems than that!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
Going old school!
PUBLIC PARKING
-------
It's coming back around!
The predator's back on 'em.
Ready missiles!
Roger that.
Fire!
Shit!
I need a lateral.
Rom, where are you?
Running back! Charging in.
Meet me on Third and Spring.
You got it!
I'm halfway there.
Grab your computer and
get in the window!
- Why?
- Do it, now!
You gotta go! Right now!
Fire!
No!
----
He made it!
Can't believe we pullled that off!
-----
Wait, we're still being hacked.
What?
God's Eye is still tracking Ramsey.
Keep the drone in pursuit of her.
The signal has to be
coming from somewhere.
Breaking news out of Los Ángeles tonight.
In what can only be
described as vehicular warfare,
police are engaged
in a high speed pursuit...
I got it. The piggyback in the hack
off that satellite tower right there.
Take it out!
Toretto.
Wait, what happened?
We were almost there.
They've cut the signal.
I can't finish the hack.
What do you mean?
------
Brian, they took out the tower!
Dad, what's going on?
Daddy's gotta go to work.
Alright, baby girl.
Elena's gonna be here in a little bit.
You know our drill.
Give me three for the road.
You thought this was
gonna be a street fight?
You're goddamn right it is.
------
There has to be another way.
Wait. I'm seeing half a dozen cell
towers between Sixth and State.
Brian, if you can get to the top of
any one of those buildings around there...
we can reroute the signal
manually and finish the job.
I'm on it.
Sir, did you hear that?
O´Conner is on foot
heading for a repeater.
He's gonna try to reinitiate the hack.
Keep the drone on the girl.
Kiet.
O´Conner's on foot somewhere
between Sixth and State.
Don't let him make it there.
Boys is on us!
And them boys ain't ready for this!
Shit!
First a tank, then a plane...
Now we got a spaceship?
That's not a spaceship, that's a drone!
Oh it's a drone?
Now you gonna break it down
and be articulate...
like you already know
what the hell is going on?
Shut your ass up and drive the car!
Letty, the football's on fire!
We need help!
Hang on! I'm coming!
Ramsey, get ready to go again.
Drone has missile lock.
Fire!
Target destroyed.
Wait! God's Eye still has her.
How can that be?
Get up. Come on.
Let's go! Let's go.
They switched her under the bridge.
What?
You gotta get outta here, it's on
your trail and it's coming fast.
Got it.
So if this car goes south,
who's coming to save us?
Save us, honey? We're it.
Where are they now?
Six blocks east, hauling ass.
Where we heading, Tej?
There's a service elevator
past the maintenance center.
It will take you directly
up to the repeater.
Brian, you gotta hurry!
Too slow!
It's coming back.
We'll lose them in the tunnel.
Got it!
Fire!
I can't shake this thing!
The predator has missile lock.
Take it out!
No way.
Wait! What happened?
Sir, someone just
double tapped our drone.
What?
Hey, did you bring the cavalry?
Woman, I am the cavalry.
Who is that?
That's Hobbs!
I'm at the repeater.
The access cable's in the base.
Just plug it into your phone
and Ramsey will be back online.
Ramsey, go!
Brian did it. We're back in.
We've got God's Eye back.
- We lost the God's Eye!
- What?
Shit!
Military's inbound.
Three minutes and closing.
We need to get
the hell outta here.
Tej, Roman, I'm on my way.
Alright, homie. I'll see you there.
I have eyes on Toretto.
Shaw's in the way.
Then it seems our
friendship is at an end.
Do it.
The thing about street fights?
The street always wins.
Goodbye, Toretto.
Take him out!
Son of a...
I need some help out here!
We're getting killed.
I need some backup!
No! Son of a bitch.
He's getting away!
No, stop them.
Don't miss.
Dom!
Come on.
C'mon, buddy.
Is he breathing?
Here's what I need you to do.
Keep his head tilted up.
All right. Keep
it back like this.
Clinch his nose, keep his head
tilted. Breathe in him now. Go.
That's good.
Come on, Dom.
Come on, goddammit!
You come on, you breathe!
Go, go, breathe!
C'mon, dammit. Let's go. Come
on, Dom! I need you to breathe.
Come on, Dom. Come back, c'mon.
Come on, buddy. Dom, come on!
Back off!
Will you stop? Breathe into him.
You breathe into him.
- You breathe into him.
- Back off!
Please, please, Dom.
Dom, baby.
I know you're hurting right now.
But I want you to listen.
Stay awake and focus on me.
I remember everything.
It came to me like a flood.
That night, in the
Dominican Republic.
The night we got married.
Who has the ring?
(Letty laughs)
Will this do?
With this silver necklace,
love...
We have eternity in this moment.
You will never be alone again.
I vow, wherever you go, I go.
You ride, I ride.
You fight, I fight.
And if you ever die on me,
Dominic Toretto...
I'm gonna die with you.
I love you, Letty.
I will always love you.
If you die, I die.
And I'm not ready to
leave this place yet.
This moment, still ours.
I remember everything.
I remember it all.
It's about time.
Oh, God.
Why didn't you tell
me we were married?
Because you can't tell
someone they love you.
Holy shit.
BLACK SITE --- CIA
You sure you brought enough
backup with you, Hobbs?
Oh, they ain't mine.
They're here to protect you.
From me killing your ass.
You do know, none of
this will keep me, right?
Well I want you to dig through 38
feet of concrete and steel...
and my fist and a bodybag will be
waiting for you on the other side.
So I suggest you get to digging, boy.
- Daddy, come play.
- Yeah.
Look at him, look at him.
Yeah, buddy.
- Duty calls.
- It does.
- Come on...
- Let's get momma...
Y'know we gotta tan because...
the sun is out, you know...
medium rare, but I can get like...
well done, like really dark.
- What you nudging me for?
- Close your mouth for two seconds.
Just open your eyes, man.
Beautiful.
That's where he belongs.
Home.
Where he's always belonged.
Things are gonna be different now.
You got it. What...
One more time.
You aren't going to say goodbye?
Yeah! Good job!
My man.
It's never goodbye.
Music: See You Again
by: Wiz Khalifa
It's been a long day
without you, my friend
And I'll tell you all about
it when I see you again
We've come a long way
from where we began
Oh, I'll tell you all about
it when I see you again
When I see you again
First you both go out your way
And the vibe is feeling strong
And what's small turn to a friendship
A friendship turn into a bond
And that bond will never be broken
And the love will never get lost
And when brotherhood come first
Then the line will never be crossed
Established it on our own
When that line had to be drawn
And that line is what we reach
So remember me when I'm gone
It's been a long day
Without you, my friend
And I'll tell you all about
it when I see you again
When I see you again
Hey, thought you could
leave without saying goodbye?
I used to say I lived my life
a quarter mile at a time.
And I think that's
why we were brothers.
Because you did, too.
- This is your car.
- My car?
You're all free.
Home, sweet home.
- What's happening, boy?
- Thanks for the invite.
Wanna go for a drive?
No matter where you are,
whether it's a quarter mile away,
or halfway across the world...
The most important thing in life will
always be the people in this room.
Right here, right now.
Salud, mi familia.
You'll always be with me.
And you'll always be my brother.
FOR PAUL